This Loo or that Loo, both look the same. There are
many such situations in life when we get
confused between the two. That is why it is
important to understand the correct comparison. Welcome
to Policy Ek. I am Sonali Joshi and today
I have brought a comparison video for you
between two hit plans of ADAC
ADAC Ergo Optima Secure vs
Restore. Before we come to the comparison of both,
understand that both the plans are from the
same insurance company. Today
in this video we are going to cover the main
differences, common features and seven basic
differences. The main difference in both these plans will be
mainly in the features. Let us now
come to their main differences. ADAC
Ergo Optima Secure is a comprehensive
medical policy which
comes with a variety of benefits such as Secure
Benefit, Value Buy Benefit, Protect
Benefit, Plus Benefit. This plan provides coverage
of medical expenses in India as well as
global health cover.
It also provides prevent health checkup and
You will also get the benefit of automatic restoration. On the
other hand, ADAC AGO Optima
Restore is a good medical coverage that takes
care of the health of individuals and their families. It has the Restore benefit,
which covers sudden or planned medical expenses
such as hospitalization,
ambulance services, day care
treatment, domicile treatment extra.
Apart from this, this policy also provides other benefits like
multiplier benefit, sheltered accommodation,
preventive health checkup. Now let's talk about the
common features in both the plans. The term
from hdfcfund.com is for 180 days. The sum insured option in both the plans is Rs
3 lakh to Rs 1 crore in Restore
and Rs 5 lakh to Rs 2 crore in Secure.
AYUSH treatments are not available in Restore, whereas
in Secure, you
get coverage for AYUSH treatments.
Talking about maternity cover,
maternity cover is available in both the options. You will
also get the option of day care in both the plans.
Now let's look at their basic
differences. First, the basic  Difference Between
ADFC and Go Optima Secure Plans
Customers get the Secure Benefit. This
health insurance plan provides additional coverage
up to 100% of the base sum insured.
This coverage starts immediately
with no extra charge. The restore benefit
in this plan is
activated when the basic
sum insured and the multiplier benefit, if
applicable, are fully or partially
utilized. This benefit is
available to all insured individuals. The
second 2x Multiply Benefit during the next claim. The
2x Multiply Benefit in ADFC Ergo Optima Secure
means that the coverage doubles.
In this plan, the insurance coverage doubles immediately.
This means that the insured
gets double the coverage from day one, without any activation or claim
requirement, and without any additional cost. Also, a
bonus of 50% is available on hdfcergo.com.  The sum assured is up to 100% only
in 2-year policies.
Multiply benefit is applicable at the end of every year.
Third, entry age:
In ADAC Ergo Optima Secure also the maximum age is
65 years and minimum is 91 days. In ADAC Ergo
Optima Restore the maximum age is 65
years and minimum is 91 days. Fourth,
discounts:
Discount of 10% is available in hdfcergo.com Secure.
If two or more members
are covered under this plan, on the other hand, if you visit hdfcergo.com,
you can avail online discount of up to 10%.
Optima Store
offers additional 7.5% discount on the
premium if a two-year policy is chosen.
Fifth, daily cash for shared accommodation:
In Optima Secure, only 800 daily cash is
available and in Optima Restore,
daily cash is 8800 per day or 000 per day for
choosing shed or accommodation. Sixth, ambulance
road
hdfc0000054 Optima Secure has sum assured options of Rs 5 lakh,
10 lakh, 15 lakh, 20 lakh, 25 lakh, 50 lakh, 1
crore and 2 crore, whereas
Optima Restore has
sum assured options of up to Rs 3 lakh, 5 lakh, 10 lakh, 20 lakh, 25 lakh, 50 lakh. So,
these were the basic
differences and options of both the plans. Now that you know this, you should
also know that both these
plans are specially designed
for the different needs of different individuals so that
their family remains financially safe.
Rest, you can choose your own plan as per your choice and needs.
PolicyX keeps
making plan comparison videos
so that you do not face any problem in choosing a plan.
That is why we are India's most
trusted insurance advisor. To avail any of these
plans, you
can visit our website; you will find the link in the description box
or you can call our toll free number
72900.  You
can get more information from expert advisor by calling 5218, that too free
of cost. If you have any insurance related
question, then do let us know by commenting,
we will try our best to answer your questions. If
you liked this video, then do
not forget to like it till then bye bye take
care and happy
[Music]
Insure h